<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="1449BC5F-EE6B-41F5-8D88-F7F8A746F60B">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090616" date="2009-06-16 10:34:22 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Choses De Notre Vie</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>We have been derelict in posting pictures. This has something to do with having too much work, but also a certain lack of energy and focus. Let&#x2019;s catch up.&#xD;&#xD;First, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/743C0191-4E9B-41CC-AD04-2C4121C012FE"&gt;pictures from our 2007 Summer in Geneva&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. Anton went to his first whole-week-away-from-home camp in Geneva. We drove him to the meeting place where he went with Yves&#x2019; daughter Oceane. He hugged Nadia and happily went off. It was great, he did not cry at all. Nadia loved Les-Bains-des-Paquis in Geneva where she read comics in French and bathed.Natasha and Deda Slava came to Geneva and the children enjoyed playing with them. Babi was clearly Anton&#x2019;s favorite. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/743C0191-4E9B-41CC-AD04-2C4121C012FE"&gt;[N]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD; &#xD;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/336DDC7E-CF0D-4B38-8D34-A0DE24C89E6A"&gt;Nadia&#x2019;s birthday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; was like a three stage rocket. We had a small birthday at our house with a cake. But then we also went to American Girl&#x2019;s place in Chicago. Nadia and her doll Molly were treated to a nice dinner with a cake and candles. Celine, Anton, Dad and Mom attended. We went to the Chicago Pier and played mini-golf and ate ice cream. Nadia&#x2019;s cake was on the back porch of our house. Finally, her main birthday was held at a pool in the Best Western hotel. All of her friends came and played for hours. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/336DDC7E-CF0D-4B38-8D34-A0DE24C89E6A"&gt;[M]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/B6DCDB33-50D1-45DA-BB10-01479C845B2B"&gt;Pot pourri.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Nadia and Olga spent a couple of days in Seattle. We had fun at home. The CS department made a new picture of Jan. The Kids played soccer and went to Taekwondo. Jan went to Montreal for the OOPSLA conference. Halloween. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/B6DCDB33-50D1-45DA-BB10-01479C845B2B"&gt;[O]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;&#x2028;The week before Christmas we went to &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/A2EB7D97-719B-4E1F-89C9-9313E2B68917"&gt;Punta Cana &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;in the Dominican Republic. This was a wonderful break from the cold and dreary Indiana winter. We loved ClubMed and would go back there any day. &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/A2EB7D97-719B-4E1F-89C9-9313E2B68917"&gt;[L]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Sunday, February 17, 2008&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="17_Catching_up_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="266px" height="200px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Catching up</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
