<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Les Vitek</title>
    <link>http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>C’est le blog de Nadia, Anton, Olga et Jan</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.1</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up</title>
      <link>http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2008/2/17_Catching_up.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4e976a4-5316-4992-be26-117e8c75c3bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 16:04:10 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2008/2/17_Catching_up_files/original.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Media/object092_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:98px; height:74px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;We have been derelict in posting pictures. This has something to do with having too much work, but also a certain lack of energy and focus. Let’s catch up.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First, &lt;a href=&quot;../N.html&quot;&gt;pictures from our 2007 Summer in Geneva&lt;/a&gt;. Anton went to his first whole-week-away-from-home camp in Geneva. We drove him to the meeting place where he went with Yves’ daughter Oceane. He hugged Nadia and happily went off. It was great, he did not cry at all. Nadia loved Les-Bains-des-Paquis in Geneva where she read comics in French and bathed.Natasha and Deda Slava came to Geneva and the children enjoyed playing with them. Babi was clearly Anton’s favorite. &lt;a href=&quot;../N.html&quot;&gt;[N]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;../M.html&quot;&gt;Nadia’s birthday&lt;/a&gt; was like a three stage rocket. We had a small birthday at our house with a cake. But then we also went to American Girl’s place in Chicago. Nadia and her doll Molly were treated to a nice dinner with a cake and candles. Celine, Anton, Dad and Mom attended. We went to the Chicago Pier and played mini-golf and ate ice cream. Nadia’s cake was on the back porch of our house. Finally, her main birthday was held at a pool in the Best Western hotel. All of her friends came and played for hours. &lt;a href=&quot;../M.html&quot;&gt;[M]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;../O.html&quot;&gt;Pot pourri.&lt;/a&gt; Nadia and Olga spent a couple of days in Seattle. We had fun at home. The CS department made a new picture of Jan. The Kids played soccer and went to Taekwondo. Jan went to Montreal for the OOPSLA conference. Halloween. &lt;a href=&quot;../O.html&quot;&gt;[O]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; The week before Christmas we went to &lt;a href=&quot;../L.html&quot;&gt;Punta Cana &lt;/a&gt;in the Dominican Republic. This was a wonderful break from the cold and dreary Indiana winter. We loved ClubMed and would go back there any day. &lt;a href=&quot;../L.html&quot;&gt;[L]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2008/2/17_Catching_up_files/original.jpg" length="171909" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer in the Czech</title>
      <link>http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/11/6_Summer_in_the_Czech.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a522e94-8b29-4658-b450-1af059ca796f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 6 Nov 2007 20:33:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/11/6_Summer_in_the_Czech_files/original.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Media/object093_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:98px; height:74px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I am finally catching and putting pictures from the children’s summer in the Czech republic.&lt;br/&gt;Nadia and Anton spent two months with Babi, Deda and Natasha in Prague and Kremze, and, to our surprise, loved it.&lt;br/&gt;They met members of our family and visited the some of the most beautiful parts of the republic. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                                      [&lt;a href=&quot;../I.html&quot;&gt; the pictures  are here&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/11/6_Summer_in_the_Czech_files/original.jpg" length="242965" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer in Prague</title>
      <link>http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/6/15_Summer_in_Prague.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96e62eec-518d-4746-b1c5-738a2bb014d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2007 22:56:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/6/15_Summer_in_Prague_files/DSC02754.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Media/object114.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:98px; height:74px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Anton’s last year at Montessori was capped by a wonderful show. Anton sang two songs, one about seeds growing up, and the other about a wonderful world. He was really enjoying himself - before the show he was the center of attention. During the first song he was the lead - center stage - and clearly the tallest of the bunch.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;                                      [&lt;a href=&quot;../H.html&quot;&gt; the pictures  are here&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We said goodbye to Lafayette and flew from Indy to Newark to Geneva to Prague. There was a little bit of stress for dad - who was flying alone with two small ones - as our plane was delayed in Newark. Twice. Once to wait for Airforce One to land and another time while waiting for the President to board and leave for Europe. In the end we made it OK and were met by RoseMarie and Jan Sr. The kids had never seen Prague but they liked it right away. It was really wonderful to see.&lt;br/&gt;We could meet our friends from Lafayette (Paul, Cecile, Marie, Anne and their latest). While Nadia did not remember the girls it did not take them long to become friends again.&lt;br/&gt;We also met with Radan and his newborn. So cute.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After that Dad flew off to Cyprus and London before returning to Lafayette.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/6/15_Summer_in_Prague_files/DSC02754.jpg" length="147333" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portraits</title>
      <link>http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/5/14_Portraits.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00597571-b0a4-43b5-b672-1281326c6e3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2007 20:26:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/5/14_Portraits_files/IMG_1671.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Media/object115.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:98px; height:74px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;For mother’s day, we went to an Italian restaurant where we took the above picture. It was, as usual for a Sunday, a work day for the parents -- Nadia and Anton where happy to see us for a little bit.&lt;br/&gt;Anton is a healthy and funny little devil who loves to make funny faces and attack his dad. Sometimes Anton and Nadia put on a “show” for us where they dance and sing. For the last show we had Anton with a spider man mask and a green --glow in the dark-- wig. &lt;br/&gt;The pictures are  [&lt;a href=&quot;../F.html&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;}  and  [&lt;a href=&quot;../E.html&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;].&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/5/14_Portraits_files/IMG_1671.jpg" length="153657" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images of Nadia</title>
      <link>http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/4/18_Images_of_Nadia.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e148fbeb-4e02-4825-ac78-787b61736384</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2007 18:16:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/4/18_Images_of_Nadia_files/IMG_1528.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Media/object116.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:98px; height:74px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Molly is Nadia’s American Girl(tm). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;She lived during the second world war, is smart (because, as Nadia says, she wears glasses) and has red pajamas.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After one of Jan’s trip to New York, Nadia received a well deserved gift. Matching pajamas.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;../D.html&quot;&gt;Pictures are Here&lt;/a&gt;]</description>
      <enclosure url="http://web.me.com/vitekj/Choses/Blog/Entries/2007/4/18_Images_of_Nadia_files/IMG_1528.jpg" length="172884" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
